{"test_questions": [[{"question": "As frequency increases", "opta": "both series and parallel RL impedance decrease", "optb": "series RL impedance decreases and parallel RL impedance increases", "optc": "series RL impedance increases and parallel RL impedance decreases", "optd": "both series and parallel RL impedance increase", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Calculate the voltage dropped across R1 in the given circuit.", "opta": "14 V", "optb": "26.8 V", "optc": "28 V", "optd": "0 V", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the true power of a 24 Vac parallel RL circuit when R = 45  and XL = 1100 ?", "opta": "313.45 W", "optb": "12.8 W", "optc": "44.96 W", "optd": "22.3 W", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If XL= 100  and R = 100 , then impedance will be", "opta": "141.4", "optb": "14.14", "optc": "100", "optd": "200", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true if the inductor shorts out in the circuit in the given circuit?", "opta": "Each component drops 5 V.", "optb": "The impedance equals 0 .", "optc": "The power factor equals 1.", "optd": "The phase angle equals 90\u00b0.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Calculate the voltage dropped across L2 in the given circuit.", "opta": "18 V", "optb": "6 V", "optc": "13.5 V", "optd": "0 V", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the magnitude of the phase angle of a 24 Vac parallel RL circuit when R = 45  and XL = 1100 ?", "opta": "0.001\u00b0", "optb": "2.3\u00b0", "optc": "87.6\u00b0", "optd": "89.9\u00b0", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true if the frequency decreases in the circuit in the given circuit?", "opta": "The phase angle decreases.", "optb": "VR", "ans": "", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "What is the magnitude of the phase angle between the source voltage and current when a 100 mH inductor with an inductive reactance of 6 k and a 1 k resistor are in series with a source?", "opta": "0.1\u00b0", "optb": "9.0\u00b0", "optc": "61.0\u00b0", "optd": "81.0\u00b0", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true if R1 opens in the circuit in the given circuit?", "opta": "IL2 increases.", "optb": "ZT decreases.", "optc": "VS increases.", "optd": "VL1 equals 0 V.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true if R = 100  and XL = 100  in the circuit in the given circuit?", "opta": "Each component drops 5 V.", "optb": "The impedance equals 200 .", "optc": "The power factor equals 1.", "optd": "The phase angle equals 45\u00b0.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true about a lag network?", "opta": "An increase in frequency causes an increase in phase lag.", "optb": "An increase in frequency causes an increase in the magnitude of the output voltage.", "optc": "A decrease in frequency causes an increase in phase lag.", "optd": "A decrease in frequency causes a decrease in the magnitude of the output voltage.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}